Before Monday, I would like you to do some research on these three things.
One, who is Russell Vaught?
I want you to know who Russell Vaught is by Monday.
I want you to know what his position is now.
And I want you to know why I want you to know who he is.
Two, by Monday, I want you to know two other Israel lobbies.
And I want you to know why they're a problem.
Everyone's talking about AIPAC.
Yeah, okay.
They're the one that everyone knows.
Do you think they're the only one?
No.
So by Monday, please be able to name two other Israel lobbies.
And also be able to name why it's a problem that we have Israel lobbies.
And three, by Monday, I want you to be able to tell me the difference between a Democrat and a leftist.
Those are words that are being thrown around very willy-nilly.
And they are being presented as if they are synonymous.
So by Monday, I want you to be able to know the difference between a Democrat and a leftist.
And the bonus is I want you to be able to name a television show that you've actually learned from.
I say this because there is trickery afoot that suggests that entertainment and programming cannot be educational.
I hate when I see the concept of, like, the stupid box, the idiot box, as if there hasn't been television that is actually not for idiots.
And as somebody who comes from that world and who creates in that mindset, I would love for you all to suggest some options.
Have a good weekend.
I believe that if white folks do not build altars on Juneteenth, they should be haunted.